[Music]
[音乐]
hi my name is Chris Haggerty I work in
嗨，我叫克里斯·哈格蒂（Chris Haggerty），我在这里工作
the Java platform group at Oracle and
Oracle的Java平台小组和
today I'm going to be talking about
今天我要说的是
handling response data with a Java 11
用Java 11处理响应数据
HTTP client in this session we're going
在此会话中的HTTP客户端
to take a high-level look at the
从高层次看
reactive streams interfaces in the Java
Java中的反应流接口
platform and how they operate using this
平台及其使用方式
knowledge we will then see how the HTTP
知识之后，我们将了解HTTP
client leverages these interfaces to
客户利用这些接口来
handle request and response bodies we'll
处理请求和响应机构
work through an example of how to write
通过一个如何写作的例子
a custom response body subscriber and
定制响应主体订户，以及
how to interoperate with existing flow
如何与现有流程互操作
publishers and subscribers before
之前的发布者和订阅者
looking at the reactive streams it is
看着反应流
useful to remind ourselves of the
有助于提醒自己
classic producer/consumer paradigm and
经典的生产者/消费者范例和
some of the potential concerns and
一些潜在的问题和
issues with it typically the producer
通常是生产者的问题
generates items or data puts them in a
生成项目或数据将其放入
queue or buffer of sorts at the same
相同的队列或缓冲区
time the consumer consumes the data by
消费者消耗数据的时间
removing items one at a time from the
一次从
buffer the problem was how to make sure
缓冲问题是如何确保
that the producer is not blocked when
当生产者没有被阻止时
the buffer becomes full or that the
缓冲区已满或
consumer is not trying to get data when
消费者在以下情况下不尝试获取数据
the buffer is empty and had a
缓冲区为空，并且有一个
notification mechanism to implement such
通知机制来实现
if it happens as well as trying to
如果发生以及尝试
determine a reasonable buffer size
确定合理的缓冲区大小
moving to reactive streams the producer
转向反应性生产者
is known as a publisher that publishes
被称为发布者
items the consumer is known as a
被消费者称为
subscriber that receives items the
接收项目的订户
publisher has a single method subscribed
发布者订阅了一个方法
that takes a subscriber the subscriber
需要一个订阅者
has four methods unsubscribe on next on
有四种取消订阅的方法
error and on complete we'll take a look
错误，完整的我们来看一下
at these now a subscriber can be
现在，这些用户可以
subscribed to a publisher by calling the
通过调用
publisher subscribed method and passing
发布者订阅的方法和传递
the subscriber the publisher den calls
订阅者，发布者拒绝致电
the subscribers unsubscribe method with
订户的退订方法
a subscription this handshake between
两次握手之间的订阅
the subscriber and the publisher results
订阅者和发布者结果
in the publisher having a reference to
在发布者中引用
the subscriber and the subscriber having
订户和订户具有
the publisher subscription
发布者订阅
that it was given in unsubscribing it is
它是在取消订阅时给出的
the subscription that acts as a
充当
mechanism for the subscriber to send
订户发送的机制
signals to the publisher for example
例如向发布者发出信号
using the subscription the subscriber
使用订阅订阅者
can request a number of items from the
可以从
publisher the publisher can then publish
发布者然后可以发布
at most that number of items by calling
最多可以致电
the subscribers our next method and
订户我们的下一个方法
number of times each with a single item
单个项目的次数
this request mechanism provides the
该请求机制提供了
subscriber with back pressure since it
订户具有背压，因为它
is in control of the maximum number of
控制最大数量
items that may be sent to it if the
如果
publisher has no more items to publish
发布者没有其他要发布的项目
then it calls subscribers on complete
然后呼叫订户
method this informs the subscriber that
通知订户的方法
the publisher regardless of demand for
发行人，无论需求如何
more items will publish no more items to
更多项目将不会发布更多项目给
dis subscriber if the publisher
Dis订阅者（如果发布者）
encounters an error say reading from a
遇到错误，请说从
file or network then it informs the
文件或网络，然后通知
subscriber of this by calling the
的订户，请致电
subscribers on error method with a
订户使用错误方法
suitable trouble indicating the problem
适当的故障指示问题
the Java platform provides support
Java平台提供支持
reactive streams to a number of
反应流到许多
interfaces in the java.util concurrent
java.util中的并发接口
flow class there is a publisher for
流类有一个发布者
publishing items a subscriber for
发布订户的项目
receiving items a subscriber subscribes
接收订户订阅的项目
to the publisher and can issue requests
给发布者，可以发出请求
for items as needed the HTTP client
用于HTTP客户端所需的项目
models request body using a subtype of
模型使用以下类型的子类型请求正文
flow publisher a request body publisher
流发布者请求主体发布者
the HTTP client subscribes to this
HTTP客户端订阅此
publisher when sending a request that
发布者在发送请求时
has body under receiving site when a
当一个
response code and headers are received
收到响应代码和标头
the HTTP client calls the body handler
HTTP客户端调用主体处理程序
the body handler can then inspect these
然后，车身搬运工可以检查这些
values if it wishes before creating a
如果愿意，可以在创建一个
body subscriber this subscriber returned
该订阅者返回的正文订阅者
by the body hunter will be used to
由身体猎人会习惯
receive and process the actual response
接收并处理实际响应
body bytes the HTTP body subscriber is a
正文字节，HTTP正文订阅者是
subtype of flow subscriber
流订阅者的子类型
and httpclient acts as a publisher of
并且httpclient充当以下内容的发布者：
response buddy bytes there are a number
响应伙伴字节中有一个数字
of factories for creating body
制造身体的工厂
publishers and body subscribers for most
大多数的出版商和团体订阅者
common use cases like publishing request
常见用例，例如发布请求
body from a string or from a file or
字符串或文件中的主体
converting response body bytes into a
将响应主体字节转换为
string or streaming them to a file in
字符串或将它们流式传输到文件中
this session we're going to focus on the
本届会议我们将重点关注
response body handler is a functional
响应主体处理程序具有功能
interface that has a single methods
具有单一方法的接口
apply that takes a response info
应用需要回复信息
containing the status code and headers
包含状态码和标题
the body handler is invoked when the
当
response status code and headers are
响应状态代码和标头为
available but before the actual response
可用，但在实际回复之前
body bytes have been received the body
正文字节已收到正文
handler can inspect response code and
处理程序可以检查响应代码并
headers before returning the body
返回正文之前的标题
subscriber the body subscriber will then
然后，主体订阅者将
be used to receive the actual response
用于接收实际的响应
body bytes body subscriber is a flow
主体字节主体订户是流
subscriber of an aggregate of byte
字节总数的订户
buffers the byte buffers contained
缓冲包含的字节缓冲区
response body bytes by the subscriber
订户的响应正文字节
has a single abstract method get' body
有一个抽象方法get'body
that returns a completion stage that
返回完成阶段
completes with a higher-level
上级完成
type that the body subscriber
输入正文订阅者
implementation will convert to response
实施将转换为响应
body bytes into the body subscriber
正文字节进入正文订阅者
class contains only study static factory
该类仅包含学习静态工厂
methods and these methods are factories
方法，这些方法是工厂
for creating body subscribers that can
用于创建可以
be used for most common use cases by
通过以下方式用于最常见的用例
converting the response body into a byte
将响应主体转换为字节
array or string or streaming it to a
数组或字符串或将其流式传输到
file or an input stream let's take a
文件或输入流，让我们
look at writing a custom body subscriber
看写一个自定义主体订户
for handling response data okay so let's
用于处理响应数据，所以让我们
take a look at how to write a custom
看看如何编写自定义
body hunger and body subscriber before
身体饥饿和身体订户之前
doing that let's take a look at how one
这样做，让我们来看看如何
of the convenience body handlers works
便利车身搬运工的工作
so here we've got a utility get method
所以这里我们有一个实用的get方法
it retrieves a given URI and returns the
它检索给定的URI并返回
response body as a string so first it
响应主体为字符串，因此首先
creates a new HTTP client over which the
创建一个新的HTTP客户端，通过该客户端
request is going
请求正在进行
he sent then it builds a request from
他发送了，然后建立了一个请求
the given URI then it calls a send async
给定的URI，然后调用发送异步
method to send a request that he uses
发送他使用的请求的方法
the body hunters of string static
字符串静态的身体猎人
factory method to create a body hunter
创建身体猎人的工厂方法
that converts the response body bytes to
将响应主体字节转换为
a string then the completable future
一个字符串，然后是可完成的未来
then apply method Maps the HTTP response
然后应用方法映射HTTP响应
of string to its body type in our cases
在我们的案例中，字符串与其主体类型有关
string and a completable future of
字符串和一个可完成的未来
string is returned so we can see example
返回字符串，所以我们可以看到示例
new such artists get methods in the main
新的此类艺术家主要获得方法
method so here we can see the get method
方法，所以在这里我们可以看到get方法
is being passed URI and then join is
被传递URI，然后加入是
being called on the complete of a future
被称为未来的完成
that's returned this blocks execution
返回这将阻止执行
until the string response body is
直到字符串响应主体为
available and then the program simply
可用，然后程序简单
prints out the body so let's run that so
打印出身体，让我们运行
here we can see the response body string
在这里我们可以看到响应正文字符串
being printed out and it's just some XML
被打印出来，它只是一些XML
this point it'd be useful to see the
在这一点上，看到
response status code so let's print that
响应状态代码，让我们打印出来
so here we use in the completable future
所以在这里我们用在可完成的未来
when complete methods to print out the
当完整的方法打印出来
status code really we should be checking
状态码我们应该检查一下
that the response value is none no in
响应值为none no in
case an error happens for simplicity
为了简单起见发生错误
then just print it for now so running
然后暂时打印它以便运行
that again okay great we can see the
再次好吧，我们可以看到
response code is 200 so everything's
响应码是200，所以一切
okay and again the response body is
好的，响应主体是
printed alright so that's everything
好了，就这样
working using one of the convenience
使用便利之一工作
body handers let's take a look at
身体处理者让我们看一下
writing our own so we need to implement
编写我们自己的，所以我们需要实施
the body subscriber interface and in
主体用户界面和
this case our type is a string
在这种情况下，我们的类型是字符串
the body subscriber has a single method
主体订户只有一种方法
called get body in a return to
叫得到身体在返回
completion stage of T T is a string in
TT的完成阶段是
our case and we must also implement the
我们的案例，我们还必须执行
four methods from flow subscriber so
流订户的四种方法
let's take a look at them we'll start
让我们看看他们，我们将开始
with the get body method so they get
用get body方法，这样他们就可以
body method needs to return a completion
body方法需要返回完成
stage of string so let's use completable
字符串的阶段，让我们使用completable
future which is a concrete
具体的未来
implementation of a completion stage
完成阶段的实施
so we've called our compatible future
所以我们称之为兼容的未来
hey buddy CF because it holds the
嘿哥们CF，因为它拥有
response body and where you can return
响应主体以及可以返回的位置
that from the cat body method now we'll
从猫的身体方法，现在我们将
move on to unsubscribe so the HTTP
继续取消订阅，以便HTTP
clients is a publisher of response body
客户是响应机构的发布者
and this string subscriber subscribe to
这个字符串订阅者订阅
that publisher so first it will have its
该发行商，因此首先它将拥有其
unsubscribe method invoked with the
用调用的取消订阅方法
subscription from the HTTP client so
来自HTTP客户端的订阅，因此
let's store that subscription
让我们存储该订阅
okay now we have the subscription we can
好吧，现在我们可以订阅了
request some more response body from the
请求其他响应主体
client or we can cancel a subscription
客户，或者我们可以取消订阅
if we're no longer interested let's
如果我们不再感兴趣，让我们
request some more and just request one
要求更多，只要求一个
at this point we can look up hook up
在这一点上，我们可以查找挂钩
error handling so we complete the body
错误处理，所以我们完成了正文
cf exceptionally after an error happens
错误发生后异常
in this simplement implementation then
在这个简单的实现中
just accumulate all of response data on
只是积累所有的响应数据
the pipe buffers in the list
列表中的管道缓冲区
and then we will convert the response
然后我们将转换响应
body into a string at the end so let's
主体最后变成字符串，让我们
create a list
建立清单
okay so every time response date is
好的，所以每次响应日期都是
received we add it to the list
收到，我们将其添加到列表中
let's keep that a better name okay great
让我们保留一个更好的名字好吧
so we're only left with the uncomplete
所以我们只剩下不完整的
method so again in this implement
方法再次在此工具中
implementation we will just determine
实施，我们将确定
the number of bytes we have put them in
我们放入它们的字节数
the byte array and then convert that
字节数组，然后将其转换
byte array into a string
字节数组转换成字符串
so once we know the number of fights are
所以一旦我们知道打架次数
remaining in each byte buffer we can sum
每个字节缓冲区中剩余的空间我们可以求和
that up so that's the total number of
那就是总数
bytes that we need in our byte array so
我们字节数组中需要的字节
let's create a fight array of that size
让我们创建一个这样大小的战斗阵列
okay now we can iterate over the buffers
好吧，现在我们可以遍历缓冲区了
and nothing to a byte array oops
字节数组什么也没有
call that buffers should be prefer over
调用缓冲区应该优先于
doc gets byte array at this point we
doc此时获取字节数组，我们
need an offsets so it's great one so
需要补偿，所以很棒
there should be zero and we need a
应该为零，我们需要一个
length and the length is going to be the
长度，长度将是
number of bytes remaining and this is
剩余的字节数，这是
offset we'll need to increase the offset
偏移量，我们需要增加偏移量
as we iterate okay now we have a
因为我们迭代好了，现在我们有一个
response body bytes in a byte array
字节数组中的响应正文字节
let's convert that to a string for
让我们将其转换为字符串
simplicity purposes we'll just ignore
简单的目的，我们将忽略
charge at conversion for now okay great
现在可以在转换时充电很好
we have our string let's complete the
我们有我们的字符串，让我们完成
body CF with that string okay at this
那个绳子的身体CF可以
point everything looks alright we forgot
一切看起来都很好，我们忘记了
one thing
一样东西
because an unsubscribe we've only
因为我们只有退订
requested one more call back every time
每次要求再打一次电话
we receive a call back we want to
我们收到回电，我们想
request another one so single step one
请求另一个，这样一个步骤
at a time okay now we have our string
好的，现在我们有了琴弦
subscriber let's hook it up with HTTP
订阅者让我们通过HTTP进行连接
clients so we need a response sorry a
客户，所以我们需要回应
your sponsor body handler here response
您的赞助人身体处理者在这里回应
party handler is a function interfaced
派对处理程序是一个接口函数
it takes for a response info returns a
响应信息需要返回一个
subscriber in our case we'll
在我们的情况下，我们将
unconditionally return a string
无条件返回字符串
subscriber okay so let's run that
订阅者好吧，让我们运行它
okay great so we've response code 200
好的，我们已经回复了代码200
again and we have our response buddy as
再次，我们有我们的反应伙伴
a string let's just take a look at
一个字符串，让我们看看
what's happening here let's add a
这里发生了什么，让我们添加一个
debugging statement to your next call
下次通话的调试语句
oops
哎呀
next it's been called with buffers and
接下来，它被称为缓冲区和
we'll change the URI so that we get some
我们将更改URI，以便获得一些
more response data okay let's run that
更多的响应数据好吧，让我们运行
again okay we can see on Nexus being
再次好吧，我们可以在Nexus上看到
called a number of times we eat by
叫我们吃饭的次数
buffers that contain the response body
包含响应主体的缓冲区
bytes they all get accumulated and then
他们都积累的字节，然后
in oncomplete
在不完整的
they get converted to a string and their
他们被转换成字符串，他们
string in this case some XML that are
在这种情况下，字符串是一些XML
very a very long line okay so now we've
非常长的线好吧，现在我们已经
seen how to write a custom body
看过如何编写自定义正文
subscriber that converts the response
转换响应的订户
body bytes into a string what if we had
正文字节转换成字符串如果我们有
a flow subscriber to an existing low
现有低点的流订户
subscriber
订户
and we wanted to use that with the HTTP
我们想将其与HTTP一起使用
clients the HTTP client only works with
客户端HTTP客户端仅适用于
buddy subscribers so let's see how we
好友订阅者，让我们看看我们如何
can make that work so first of all the
可以做到这一点，所以首先
flow subscriber doesn't have a get buddy
流订户没有好友
method and it also doesn't have a buddy
方法，它也没有伙伴
CF for simplicity let's just print out
CF为简单起见，我们只打印一下
the error if one were to occur I can
如果发生错误，我可以
remove this here
在这里删除
so the flow subscriber still needs some
因此流订阅者仍然需要一些
way of exposing its data so let's give
公开其数据的方式，让我们给
it a private field string to hold its
它是一个专用字段字符串来保存其
body and an accessor get body to return
主体和访问器使主体返回
the body okay in the uncomplete now we
身体还不错，现在我们还不完整
need to set the body field okay so now
需要设置好身体区域，所以现在
we are string subscriber which is an
我们是字符串订户，这是一个
implementation of a flow subscriber how
流订户的实现方式
can we use this with the HTTP client
我们可以将其与HTTP客户端一起使用吗
well the HTTP client provides
HTTP客户端提供的很好
convenience static factory methods that
方便的静态工厂方法
adapt between flow subscriber and body
在流量使用者和身体之间适应
subscriber so let's use one of those
订户，所以我们使用其中之一
so there's two variants of the from
因此，有两种来自的变体
subscriber adapter the first takes just
用户适配器首先需要
a subscriber and the other takes a
一个订户，另一个订一个
subscriber with a finisher function
具有装订器功能的订户
we're going to use the latter because we
我们将使用后者，因为我们
need to extract the data from the string
需要从字符串中提取数据
subscriber and to complete the HTTP
订户并完成HTTP
computable future with that value so
具有这种价值的可计算未来
your new string subscriber or use the
您的新字符串订阅者或使用
string subscriber get body methods to
字符串订阅者获取正文方法
extract the data from the flow
从流中提取数据
subscriber instead of using a new string
订户，而不是使用新字符串
subscriber here we can use the body
用户可以在这里使用主体
subscriber okay let's run that
订阅者好吧，让我们运行
again we can see all that on next
再一次，我们可以看到所有的一切
implications and we have the response
暗示，我们有回应
body as a string again we can simplify
主体再次作为字符串我们可以简化
this even further instead of using a
这甚至可以代替使用
body subscriber directly the body
主体订阅者直接将主体
handlers and body handler classes expose
处理程序和主体处理程序类公开
factory methods of similar names so
相似名称的工厂方法
let's use one of those instead
让我们使用其中之一
okay so we don't need to land here
好，所以我们不需要在这里降落
anymore should we only just a buddy
我们应该只是一个伙伴吗
handler directly so that's really not to
直接处理程序，所以实际上不是
make sure it works okay great
确保它可以正常工作
same output so we've seen how to write a
相同的输出，所以我们已经看到了如何编写一个
custom body Handler and also how to
自定义主体处理程序以及如何
adapt a flow subscriber to the HTTP body
使流订阅者适应HTTP正文
handler or body subscriber there are a
处理程序或正文订阅者
number of adapter methods that support
支持的适配器方法数量
inter operation between regular flow
规则流之间的互操作
types like slow publisher and slow
缓慢的发布者和缓慢的类型
subscriber and their HTTP client
订户及其HTTP客户端
equivalents the one we just seen being
相当于我们刚刚看到的
used in a demo from subscriber has two
订户演示中使用的有两个
variants the first just accepts a flow
第一个只是接受流程
subscriber and returns a body subscriber
订户并返回正文订户
avoid in this case the response body is
在这种情况下，避免响应主体为
not being made available through the
无法通过
HTTP response but instead through some
HTTP响应，但通过一些
other mechanism like an entry in the
其他机制，例如
database the second variant supports a
数据库第二种变体支持
finisher function that will be applied
将应用的装订器功能
after the death subscriber has completed
死亡订户完成后
and we seen an example of this in the
我们在
demo there are also a similar pair of
演示中也有类似的一对
methods from Lion subscriber that
来自Lion订户的方法
interoperate with flow subscribers of
与以下用户交互：
string where the response body data is
响应正文数据所在的字符串
converted to a flow of string lines and
转换为字符串流并
sent to the flow subscriber line by line
逐行发送到流订户
this is somewhat analogous to
这有点类似于
bufferedreader read lines or the nio
bufferedreader读取行或行
files Lions method that returns a stream
返回流的Lions文件方法
of lines in a file
文件中的行数
there are also equivalent adapters on
也有等效的适配器
the sending side for request body to
请求正文的发送方
summarize the HTTP client treats boat
总结HTTP客户端对待船
requests and response body as reactive
请求和响应主体为反应性
streams so gets the benefits of
流因此获得的好处
asynchronous programming with
异步编程
non-blocking backpressure
无阻塞背压
we seen how to write a custom body
我们看到了如何编写自定义正文
subscriber implementation that behaves
行为良好的订户实现
similar to the convenience body
与便利机构相似
subscriber returned by body subscribers
正文订阅者返回的订阅者
of string
字符串
ttp client provides a number of adapters
ttp客户端提供了许多适配器
for interoperating with existing
与现有的互操作
reactive streams publishers and
反应流发布商和
subscribers you can download java 11 now
订阅者，您可以立即下载java 11
at this URL please join us at open JDK
在此URL上，请在开放的JDK中加入我们
or follow us on Twitter at openjdk or
或在openjdk的Twitter上关注我们，或
hashtag Java 11 my own twitter handle is
我自己的Twitter句柄是Java 11
at checker 999 oracle is the steward of
在检查器999甲骨文是
java providing a large amount of
java提供了大量的
development engineering funding for the
开发工程资金
Java SE platform and open JDK oracle
Java SE平台并打开JDK oracle
provides leading class premier support
提供一流的总理支持
for a low cost that's easy to purchase
易于购买的低成本
with simple pricing tiers thank you for
具有简单的定价等级谢谢
watching
观看
[Music]
[音乐]